(Leonard:)I know it only takes
one doctor's finger.
(Amy:)Hello.
(Leonard:)We should let
you guys talk.
(Howard:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)You don't have to leave.
Look at me go!
(Amy:)Uh, Bernadette,
you're my ride.
BERNADETTE:
Walk!
(Amy:)How have you been?
(Sheldon:)I'm doing all right.
(Sheldon:)I tried fencing today.
(Amy:)How'd that go?
(Sheldon:)It was pretty easy.
(Sheldon:)And I think my background
in "mathletics" helped.
(Sheldon:)Barry Kripke was there.
(Sheldon:)I should let you know
(Sheldon:)that he expressed interest
in asking you out.
(Amy:)Well, actually,
he-he already did.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)But don't get
too attached to him.
(Sheldon:)In two years, 364 days,
he's a dead man.